(Howard:)You believe in your religion,
I'll believe in mine.
(Amy:)How's it going
in there?
(Penny:)Eh.
(Penny:)Not really a great outfit
for work,
(Penny:)unless something opens up in
the hookers and whores division.
(Penny:)Hey, can I ask you
something?
Sure.
(Penny:)Do I really force you
to do things you don't want to?
(Amy:)Yeah, but it's okay.
(Penny:)How is it okay?
(Amy:)I promised myself,
if I ever got friends,
(Amy:)I'd do whatever they said.
(Amy:)Really, I'm lucky you found me
before a cult did.
(Penny:)Well, you know,
that was a long time ago.
(Penny:)You're a different woman now.
You're smart,
(Penny:)you've got great friends,
you've got a boyfriend,
(Penny:)you're pretty, you have
zero fashion sense, but...
(Penny:)Anyway, tonight we're gonna do
whatever you want.
(Amy:)Really?
(Penny:)Absolutely.
You name it, we're doing it.
(Amy:)Basket weaving
at the craft museum.
(Penny:)Well, you named it.